{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"﻿alumin","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"ljeti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"djeti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cr","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"četverod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tetički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tetika","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dl","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dod","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"don","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dvod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"financ","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"garson","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gluhon","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gluhosl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gn","osnova2":"zdo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"jednod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kar","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kasn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kl","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"nje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"kanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kvoc","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"gati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"po","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"rica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ska","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"litan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"lit","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"čni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"napr","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"nesv","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"nevr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"obav","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"oduv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"osm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"oždr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"podn","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pol","osnova2":"vati (se)","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podnevni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"dlog","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"dložni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"laz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"nos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podnevni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"tka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"redosl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"č","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"dak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tkost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"po","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"spr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"mski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"str","osnova2":"lac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"str","osnova2":"lčev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ćnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tliti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"širokobr","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"kom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"T","osnova2":"lovo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lovski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"trod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"umr","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"un","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"upotr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"usl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zapov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"be","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"biti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bd","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"lokošćanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"loruski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"žati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"dilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bogin","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"branitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bro","osnova2":"vni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"brzinom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"buđen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cijukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"dilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovitost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"včica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"crn","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"crven","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cvil","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"ćarna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"ćarnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čekan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"češljan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četverom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četveror","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četveros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čin","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"desetl","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"desetom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"devetom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dil","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čačić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čačićev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"dovina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"latnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"litelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvoran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvorno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvornost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"telina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tešce","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tinjstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vičanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dod","osnova2":"ljivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"događan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dokol","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dokol","osnova2":"nka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dol","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"doživ","osnova2":"ti ","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"družen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"drvl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dubinom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"stoti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvo","osnova2":"zičan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvor","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvos","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvot","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"fijukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"fotokopiran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"kad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"koji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"što","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"što","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gledatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gor","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"govoren","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"grabl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"grobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gus","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ht","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"hvalosp","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"in","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"istraživan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izdan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"iznenađen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"šćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"štavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jačan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"vački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"javnobil","osnova2":"žnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"cati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"čati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaesterac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaestero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaesti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danput","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dini","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dinica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"diničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dino","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnačen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnako","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnakost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dninski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnodimenzijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnodimenzionalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokatni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokatnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokratan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokrevetni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnoredan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnoslov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnosoban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostih","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostruk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnot","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"drilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dva","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ftin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"len","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lovnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ruzalemski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"sen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"senski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"senji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"tra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zgra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičavost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovl","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"žinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kamen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kastan","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kinopro","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kinopro","osnova2":"ktor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"kakav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kokodakan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kopl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"korišten","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"vstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kukurikan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kutom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"ran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"rno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"rnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"lica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lišavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lizan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pota","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"stve","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"šnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"man","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"dić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mijaukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mišl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"hur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"kara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"tski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"množen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"sti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"ravati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"štaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nasel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nasil","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"can","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catel","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"čaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"natkol","osnova2":"nka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazdravl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazivl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazivoslovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"negd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"div","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"divo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"divost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nesv","osnova2":"snost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"njakan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"gov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"govati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"zin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"žavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"ktni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"siti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oblikoslovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obl","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obl","osnova2":"tnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obrazovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"odgojitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"kivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"održavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduziman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ogr","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"om","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"opkoračen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"orgul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oruž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"osiguran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"čki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tiljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"osmom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ovd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ozl","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pamćen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pas","osnova2":"menik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pečen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pel","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"per","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"peteros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"petom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pitan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"smarica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ščanik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"plav","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"podnož","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"područ","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poglavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"dinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"dini","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"polet","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pol","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ponašan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poosobl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poslovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posto","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pošten","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poštovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"potkrovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"stica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"tarac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"davati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnikovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predsobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predvor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prep","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preuziman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prevoditel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pričan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prid","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prid","osnova2":"vni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prijatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"rice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"primor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prip","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prizeml","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"priznan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pročel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"ktil","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"ktor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"daona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"daonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prov","osnova2":"ravati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prov","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"putovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"putovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"raskriž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ravnatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"razdobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"roditel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rođen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rolan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rubl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sara","osnova2":"vski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sav","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sedmom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"siv","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"cište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"kira","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistočni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistok","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapadni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"skladatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sklopovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"deći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"rno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"rnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"smršav","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"gović","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stvaran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sub","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sub","osnova2":"ktni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sučel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sud","osnova2":"lovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"din","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"susn","osnova2":"žica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sut","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svid","osnova2":"ti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ćica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"sno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"snost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"stan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tiljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tionik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"že","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"žina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šestom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"škljocan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"školovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šljapkan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šupl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lesni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"rati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tlakom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"toplom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trešn","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tro","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tror","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trot","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tun","osnova2":"vina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"učen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"učitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ugl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"šan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"utemel","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"caj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"cajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"cati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vesel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vis","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"više","osnova2":"zičan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"višem","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"višet","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ronauk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitel","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šala","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"štica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ština","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"verica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbeničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vodom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vrhn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vrt","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaglavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaht","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"čati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaniman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zap","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zavid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zav","osnova2":"sa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbrajan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zd","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zdravl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zelen","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zlostavljan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"znan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zdača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zdica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"znica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"zo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žrtvovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žud","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
